

MATTEO LENOCI DATA SCIENTIST | AI & ML

- in @matteolenoci
- info@matleno.com
- **2** +39 3408242347
- matleno.com
- ♠ Via Del Circuito 285, Pescara

In my 20s I gained a lot of experience as a salesman, traveling the world and training teams of people.

In addition, my real passions are IT, data and statistics, so I have completed my master's degree on that topics.

Using my passions to provide value in my work is my dream.

Dynamic and athletic, I am also an eclectic music lover.

Few words, yet the right ones, describe me.

IT SKILLS

- R
- Python
- SQL
- Adobe Suite
- Tensorflow
- PyTorch
- Google Cloud
- Power BI

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Discipline
- Public speaking
- Critical thinking
- Strategic Planning

LANGUAGE

- Italian: Native Language
- English: C1

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aptar∡

Data Scientist | Al & ML Expert Aptar s.p.a. | April 2022 - today

- Implementing Al solutions for use in classification / predicting business outcomes.
- Analyzing customers behavior and interpret trends or patterns in complex data sets
- Performing data visualization



Networking Manager

MyVitaly srl | October 2018 - April 2022

- Held weekly meetings with customers and suppliers to identify techniques to overcome sales obstacles.
- Developed working relationships with front-line leaders.
- Coached employees in successful selling methods



Networking Manager Evergreenlifeproducts srl | 2013 - 2018

- Resolved customer issues quickly and managed over 300 accounts to increase sales and meet quotas.
- Grew retail sales volume in assigned territory (UK, USA, France, Italy) through strategic budgeting and product promotion.
- Public speaker and team builder in internal company meetings and commercial meetings

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION

Master's Degree in "Economics and Business Analytics"



Università degli studi "G. D'Annunzio" November 2020 - November 2022

- Cum Laude
- Thesis "NLP: Predictive Justice"



Bachelor's degree in "Economics and business administration"



Training course "Structogram", Bologna

3 training days about management and leadership

Autorizzo il trattamento dei dati personali contenuti nel mio curriculum vitae in base all'art. 13 del D.lgs 196/2003 e all'art. 13 del Regolamento UE 2016/679 realtivo alla protezione delle persone fisiche con riguardo al trattamento dei dati personali.